ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 5981 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II: OVERSIZE/HAT WORKER
  - Leichter, Sarah., 1948-1968 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 46 Includes: Leichter, 5/68 Convention; Leichter addressing NY Millinery Strikers, 1/63; GEB meeting Montreal 6/58 with Mayor and Mme Sarte Fournier; 1959 Convention Leichter; 10th Convention Lei
  - Lewis, Mark., 1950-1961 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 47 Includes: Lewis and Mendelowitz; Lewis portraits; 8th convention; 7th convention (?) 1950; 9th convention; A. Mendelowitz, Marx Lewis and S. Hershkowitz; Marx Lewis addressing Herman Finkelste
  - Liberal Party., 1961-1969 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 48 Includes: John Lindsay, Fioravanti G. Perotta, Sandford D. Gorelik, NYC, July 1969; Fillen O DeNovellis (United Shoe Workers); 1965 Dr. Timothy Costello, John V. Lindsay, Milton Mollen; Libera
  - Lindsay, John. V., 1965-1969 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 49 Includes: Lindsay, Fioravante F. Perotta and Sanford D. Gorelik 10/69; Fileno DiNovelis (Shoe Workers Union), mayor's reception prior to inauguration; Lindsay portrait House of Representatives
  - Lucia, Carmen., 1948-1968 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 50 Includes: May 1968 convention Lucia; 9th convention; Lucia (L. 95) 1947 portrait; 1948 convention Lucia; 1959 convention Lucia; Lucia and ITU delegate Lewis Herrman (NJ) at convention; 1964 Lu
  - Ma-Mz., 1948-1971 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 51 Includes: Margaret Mahr; 9th Convention Mahr, Alex Rose; 5/68 Convention George Marlin, Rose; 2/63 Marlin portrait; Alfred May; 1959 Convention Al May, Rose; 8th convention Bernell McDonnell
  - Massachusetts Joint Board. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 52 Includes: Mass. Jt. Bd.
  - Meany, George., 1953-1967 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 53 Includes: Meany accepts plaque from MDA, Jerry Lewis, at 12/11/67 Convention; Meany with 1966 National March of Dimes poster child; Ralph Bellamy, Meany; Meany, Alex Rose, George Meany Testimo
  - Mendelowitz, Abraham., 1962-1967 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 54 Includes: aid to cancer research, Sarah Leichter, Dr. David Habif, Murray Zuckerman, George Fleitman, Dr. Samuel Madell, Isidore Fishman, Charles Green, Dr. Manus Ornstein 1967; Mendelowitz Me
  - Millinery Institute of America., 1971 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 55 14th convention, 10/71, Charles Rothenberg (MIA); Alex Rose, Charles Rothenberg 5/68 convention; plaques dedicated to Abraham Mendelowitz and Walter K. Marks 12/6/67 plaque presentation: Dr. S
  - Millinery Label., 1960 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 56 Includes: 6/1960 Milly Label, Chas. Rothenberg
  - Millinery Promotion., 1956-1962 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 57 Includes: Robert Wagner (NYC) congratulates "Miss. Union Maid of 1962" and "Maids-in-Waiting"; Spector, Joan Crawford, Celeste Holm, Eleanor Seonle Whitney, Mendelowitz, Betsy Palmer; Robert S
  - Millinery Stabilization Commission. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 58 Includes: Professor Paul Brissenden, Isaac Siegmeister, Nathaniel Spector, Max Meyer, A. Mendelowitz; 6th or (7th) Convention Max Zaritsky, Mrs. Richard J. Bernhard; 6th Convention Mrs. Richa
  - N., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 59 Includes: Ralph Nader, 1968; Louis J. Marciante, NJ Fed Labor; Vincent Murphy, NJ Fed Labor Newark, NJ
  - National Cap and Cloth Hat Institute., 1961 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 60 Includes: 2/61 St. Louis Cap Promotion: Isadore Drucker, Jean Gillam, Morris Kean, Hyman Matlof, Ben Hian, Al Smoke, Ed Myers, Frank Novoson; Cap Institute- signing articles of incorporation:
  - New York Joint Board., 1943-1965 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 61 Includes: 2/20/43 Hotel Astor CB Agreement signing, Millinery Manufacturers of NJ and Millinery Workers Union (L. 2-24-30-42-90): Max Grossman, Harry H. Baum, Alexander Fromman (?), Al Hoffman
  - New York Millinery Health and Welfare Funds., 1953-1967 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 62 Includes: 20th anniversary cake; 3/67 Murray Zuckerman, George Fleitman, Alex Rose, Bert Goldstein; Millinery Health Fund Luncheon Astor Hotel 12/24/65: N. Spector, George Morlin, A. Mendelowi
  - Novaco, James V., 1954 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 63 Includes: 10th Convention Novaco speech; Novaco points out last rose of summer; Novaco in front of his house; Novaco and Brandon Vincent Rupolo read trip diary; 9th convention Novaco speech; N
  - O., 1946-1948 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 64 Includes: 6th or 7th convention Mayor William O'Dwyer; 6th convention-1948 O'Dwyer; 5th convention-1946 O'Dwyer; 6th convention O'Dwyer; Lucy Oppenheim portrait; testimonial to Lucy Oppenheim
  - Pa-Pz., 1963 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 65 Includes: Judge Samuel Null, Judge Jacob Panken, Nathaniel Spector; Mrs. Esther Peterson, President Lyndon B. Johnson; Daniel Pollack 11/63; Mendelowitz, Henry Pollack, Walter Marks, Alex Rose
  - "Plymouth Corporation" Plymouth, Mass scenes. (Box 38, Folder 20)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 66 Includes: "Pilgrims" reading the Bible, wearing hats; interior of replica Warren house; Mayflower II and Shallop at State Pier Plymouth, Mass.; interior of Warren House at Plymouth Plantation,
  - Ra-Rz., 1948-1970 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 67 Includes: N. Spector, Joseph Rabinovich, Harry Samet; 5/10/69 Promontory Utah ceremony, Union Pacific Engine #119, 21st infantry; bridge construction, Green River, Wyoming, Citadel Rock; Walte
  - Rich, Jacob C., 1962-1965 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    Collection was re-organized - this was formerly box 10, ff 68 Includes: 12/30/64 Rich; 1962 Convention Rich; portraits; group shots; GEB meeting at Camp Tamiment Rich retires from Hat Worker; International Labor Press Association with President Truman on
  - Rose, Alex., 1950-1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Includes: portrait; Atlantic Labor Press Conference; Rose, 5/68 convention; Rose, 1962 convention; Idlewild Airport Mr. and Mrs. Rose; Mayor's conference on organization of taxi-cab workers March 1965; Jacob Potofsky, Harry VanArsdale, A. Phillip Randolph
  - Sa-Sz., 1956-1968 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Includes: Diana Sands; Diana Sands (black actress), Mrs. Shirley Sands (L. 24) 1965; VP Jesse Scheinin 1962 convention; Jesse Scheinin 1959 convention; VP Jesse Scheinin 1962 speech; Scheinin, Martha Kasper, Lilliman Hurley, Wallace Peterson (L. 89); L. 8
  - St. Louis Joint Board., 1950-1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Includes: Isadore Drucker, Morris Kean, Jean Gillam 1962; 7th convention; 1950 7th convention, Zaritsky; 5/53 Gold Honorary Membership Card recipients; L. 17 group shot, check presentation; (black) woman receives certificate
  - Shops- Workers at Various Operations in Production of Headwear., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Includes: 1976 Felt Hat factory, Stevens Hat Mfg. Co. St. Joseph, Missouri: blocking, hydraulic king molds
  - Silcoff, Maurice., 1947-1968 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Includes: 5/68 convention Silcoff, 30th Anniversary 9/18/65; Silcoff 1962 Convention; Paul Pichette, Allen J. Mac Eachen, Silcoff, Israel Bond Dinner honoring Silcoff 2/9/64; Louis Tankel, Sarah Leichter, Silcoff 1962 Convention; Convention 1948 M.F. Gree
  - Spector, Nathaniel., 1945-1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Includes: 9th convention N. Spector 1956; portraits; Spector 5/68 Convention; Spector 1959; 7/63 Joseph Rabinovich, Spector, Founders Medal; 1/63 Spector interviewed on "Labor Press Conference" radio show; 11/63 Spector addresses convention, NY State AFL-
  - Spotlight on a Union. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Includes: presentation of History Spotlight on a Union by author Don Robinson to Zaritsky; 6th convention
  - T., 1947-1962 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Includes: Minnie Teitlebaum (L. 7) 1947; 6th convention 1948 Max Goldman, Minnie Teitlebaum; 7th convention 1950 Minnie Teitlebaum; Minnie Teitlebaum 8th convention; Minnie Teitlebaum addressing Herman Finkelstein's 65th Birthday Dinner, Hotel New Yorker
  - Triangle Fire. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Includes: viewing the bodies; extinguishing the fire; women linking arms; mourners wreckage
  - Unions Israel Tour- Nov. 1962. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Includes: Israeli military policeman, Bedouin tribesman on camel; Isaac Hamlin, Isadore Drucker, Yehoshva Levy, Mrs. Zaritsky; Albert Husyt, guide to Israel delegation; group shots; youth center; meetings; Adam Kasdi, Ephraim DuLuck; Afro-Asian Institute
  - Union Label., 1958-1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Includes: Atlanta, GA May 1971 Harry Klapper (L. 95), Michael V. Liloia; 5/70 NY State Union Label Show Albany; Albany 1970 NY State Convention of Union Label and Service Industries; 6/69 15th Empire State Labor-Management Exhibit: Alfred Smoke, Gerald Co
  - Union Label., 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Includes: George Kuezevich, Mrs. Fromkin, Helen Lemon, Sadie Twyford, Mary Lou Palmer; Vincent Impletteri, Martin Lacey, James Quinn, Harry Avrutin, Herman Finkelstein; Local 60 at 9/29-9/30 1962 convention of Pennsylvania Union Label and Service Trades d
  - Union Label. (One oversize photo moved to box 4OP), 1949-1964 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Includes: 1961 show; Howard Pickett, Jack Rosen; Canada show; Arthur Harckham, Moe Rosen, Governor Harriman (NY), Thomas Murtha, Al Manuti, Marx Lewis, Harry Avrutin; Detroit Union/Industries Show 1961; 4/61 Cobo Hall Detroit; Union Label Conference: Samu
  - U-V., 1959-1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Includes: W.J. Usery, Chief Justice Warren E. Burger, Ford, Melvin Usery, White House swearing-in 2/16/76; 1962 convention Alex Rose, Harry Van Arsdale; 1962 convention LeRoy Brown, Alex Rose, Harry Van Arsdale Jr.; 1959 Convention Harry Van Arsdale
  - Wa-Wz., 1957-1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Includes: Louis Waldman: 5th convention Zaritsky, Waldman, Mendelowitz; W. Willard Wirtz portrait; Workmen's Circle Branch 600 50th anniversary 3/19/67; Irving Helfman, Jacob Zuckerman, Rose, Norman Goldstein, Murray Zuckerman, Jack Roefe, Max Stern, Phil
  - Wagner, Mayor Robert F, Jr.., 1956-1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Includes: 10th convention; Wagner, Cecilia Martinez 10th convention; 9th convention 1956; portrait; 1962 convention; Liberal Party Dinner 10/61; 1959 Wagner; Escort Committee with Wagner 1959 Convention: Alfred Meninno (L. 15), Annie Mae Gaines (L. 125),
  - Winn, Samuel. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Includes: Sam Winn (L. 5), Senator Paul Douglas; Winn 8th Convention; Sam Winn (L. 5), Sally Fields (L. 52), I.H. Goldberg (L. 24), Julius Ginsberg, Stanley L. Johnson; (black) woman speaking; Winn, Bernard Jacobson, Sally Fields, I.H. Goldberg
  - Z., 1964-1971 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Includes: portrait Murray Zuckerman; 6/66 Murray Zuckerman, Murray Fleshner, A. Mendelowitz; 5/65 Convention Murray Zuckerman; 7/71 Theodore A. Zelewski at AFL-CIO Engineering Institute, University of Wisconsin; George Burdon, Ted Zelewsky 1/64
  - Zaritsky, Max., 1944-1969 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Includes: Youth Center, Bet Shan, 5/69 Zaritsky Memorial in Israel; 11/62 laying cornerstone for Zaritsky Memorial; 11/63 Zaritsky Center Bet Shan; Mendelowitz, Sarah Leichter, Bardacke; 6/62 check presented to Gregory Bardacke; 11/61 Montreal Milliners l
  - Zuckerman, Max., 1921-1925 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 20 Includes: Max Zuckerman funeral, Mt. Hebrong Cemetary; Sonia and Max Zuckerman's graves; 9/4/21 couple; portraits; 14th Biennial Convention U.C.H. and C.M. of N.A.; 1912 family photo postcard; 4/26/
  - Cap Industry. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 21 Includes: cap makers; Moe Steinberg shop, NY cutting caps, the Cap Makers' Chapel, Coventry Cathedral ruins, England; shop
  - Headwear Industries., 1956 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 22 Includes: hat making; forming the hat; coating hat with oil; Sam Hershkowitz, Jacob Roberts, Louis Haiman, Jacob Margolis, Judah Gertler; dope mixers, Dynel hats; Dynel plant of Carbide and Carbon C
  - Millinery Industry., 1958-1966 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 23 Includes: 10/66 women's work, millinery-shop; (black) man casting molds; preparing new line; craftsman wet-blocks a hat body; High School of Fashion Industries 1958; fashion show, High School of Fas
  - Local No. 2. New York., 1940-1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 24 Includes: Herschell Chanin; 5/68 Convention Herschell Chanin; Cornell University 5/69 course, Louis Makler, Herschell Chanin; Max Harlem; 5/67 Steward's course; painting of FDR presented in 1940 by
  - Local No. 3, New York. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 25 Includes: L. 3 Ex. Bd.
  - Local No. 4. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 26 Includes: 7th convention H. Sherman; Phillip Block; Sam Trager, H.R. Sherman, H.W. Adelman
  - Local No. 5 Chicago., 1962 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 27 Includes: L. 5 Delegates: 1962 convention
  - Locals 7 and 8, New York. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 28 Includes: Stanley Zaleski; Max Finger (L. 8), Max Zaritsky (L. 7) Nathan Hutt
  - Locals 10 and 11, Danbury., 1962 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 29 Includes: Danbury Fife and Drum Corps- Inaugural Parade; Louis Esposito (L. 10), 1962 Convention; wall pushed in at Mallory; Brewer on what remains of parking lot at Mallory; Paul Martin Hat Co. Inc
  - Locals 13 and 14, Newark., 1958 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 30 Includes: ACWA picket line, NJ: Martin Bacon, Bruno Sorchinski, Charles Marciante, Michael Liloia, Hyman Goldberg, Richard Lynch; Patrick McGovern, M. Liloia (L. 13); W. Harding (L. 14), Patrick McG
  - Local No. 15, Norwalk. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 31 Includes: speech; Trimmers local-Norwalk; Hat Corp. of America on Strike; 6th convention; 7th convention; lawyer from Bridgeport; James Novoco; 9th Convention; Hatters Union HQ; 9th convention Paul
  - Local No. 17, St. Louis., 1959 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 32 Includes: Jean Gillam 1959 convention; Selma Blassie, Elizabeth Franklin, Ethel Burkhardt, Jean Gillam, Jennie Mitchell, Isadore Drucker, Ben Fingers (?)
  - Locals 22 and 41, Los Angeles., 1952 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 33 Includes: group shots; 6/14/52 Testimonial Dinner: Sam Young and wife, Abraham Dwinsky and wife, Hans Braun, Joseph Callas, Minnie Callas, Isadore Drucker and wife, Harry Lea, Sam Nesnansky, Jack Ro
  - Local No. 23, West Upton. (Box 39, Folder 15)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 34 Includes: Helen Goodrich, Nicholas Celozzi, Eileen Henry; Helen LaBrie, Ed Erwin, Eileen Henry, Angelina Figlioli, Carrol Hixon, Nicholas Celozzi
  - Local No. 24 New York (No. 1)., 1948-1968 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 35 Includes: 4/62 group shots; Morris Hacker, Murray Zuckerman, Timothy Costello, Charles Garrahan 9/68; L. 24 group 1962 convention; 10th convention Gussie Leichter L. 24; 9th convention Murray Zucker
  - Local No. 24 New York (No. 2)., 1944-1959 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 36 Includes: Murray Zuckerman, Michael Arnon, Yehuda Tyberg, George Fleitman, Bert Goldstein, Jerome Greenberg Health Fund aids Israel cause; L. 24; 10th convention, Harry Litman, Jack Press; L. 24 50t
  - Local No. 30 New York. (Box 39, Folder 18)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 37 Includes: document signing
  - Local No. 35, Winnipeg., 1963 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 38 Includes: 1963 A. Lee, Joyce Anderson, Vicki Dubick, Irate??? Kaltenschnee, J. Sewell, Stella Banish, John Globush, Maurice Silcoff, L. Tomchyshym, Joe Meslin; Max Zaritsky, S. Herbst
  - Local No. 36, Montreal., 1960-1963 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 39 Includes: negotiations 6/63; Maurice Silcoff, Paul Pichette; Marx Lewis, pension checks, Jack Finegold, Hector Brazeau, Max Roody, Maurice Silcoff, Paul Pichette, M. Rosenbloom, Isadore Goldin, Jaco
  - Local 37-38., 1967 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 40 Includes: L. 38 dinner Donald Fraser, Isadore Drucker; Doris Bluhm, L. 38, with Golden Anniversary Birthday Cake; Edith Seliger, Frances Swanson, Doris Bluhm, Eva Hallfin, Richard Springer, Donald F
  - Local No. 42, New York., 1964 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 41 Includes: John McDonald, Max Goldman's 70th Birthday Celebration 10/64; Millinery blockers house warming; 8th convention; group shots: Salvatore Palillo, Harvey Davis, William Szabo, Alex Gold, Morr
  - Local No. 45 Philadelphia. (Box 39, Folder 23)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 42 Includes: 6th Convention; group shot, Ben Cohen
  - Locals 46 and 47, Toronto. (Box 39, Folder 24)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 43 Includes: L. 41 Toronto (UCHC MWIU), Mendel Berger and others; Mrs. D. Archer, wife of O.F.L. President David Archer L. 46; L. 46 40th Anniversary Dinner, Sid Merson; L. 46 40th Anniversary Dinner,
  - Local No. 49, Montreal., 1951-1969 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 44 Includes: Cyprieu Mirov, Alex Rose, 2/23/58; 10/59 Buckley-Brooks pact signed; Montreal meeting 9/51; 4/60 The Hat Mart, picket; 1961 assembly; picket line at Metro Hat Co.; picketing, Hy Levine; ne
  - Local No. 50, Montreal., 1961-1962 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 45 Includes: 1962 Convention Francis Moran (L. 92), Jenny Wiseman (L. 50); 2/8/61 1st Annual Dinner of L. 50, Montreal: S.D. Cohen, Maurice Silcoff, Frances Moran, Danny Radow, Paul Pichette; 2/8/61 ne
  - Miscellaneous Montreal Locals. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 46 Includes: donations for Israel L. 49 Silcoff, Alvin Bronstein, Pichette, N. Titleman, Rosenblatt, Cooperberg; Locals 36 and 49; Rose, Pichette, Silcoff, Jt. Bd. Meeting; 10th Convention Locals 36 an
  - Canada- Miscellaneous., 1961-1964 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 47 Includes: Mrs. Patrick, wife of Windsor, Ontario mayor, being fitted for hats by L.H. Rosen; Arne Geiser, Maurice Silcoff, Canadian Labour Congress convention, 4/64 Montreal w/ Kalmen Kaplansky, Ain
  - Local No. 52, Chicago., 1962-1965 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 48 Includes: leafleting in Chicago against Leslie- James, millinery manufacturer of Los Angeles 2/65; 1962 Convention Chicago delegates; 1//63 St. Mike Glendale Novelty Co.; 10th Convention Chicago del
  - Locals 55 and 56, St. Louis. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 49 Includes: Minnie Gehring, Leo Tabachnik, Robert Nassauer, Ben Schneider, Percy Ginsburg, Joseph DeMarco; negotiating committee Union meeting; Theodes Lyles, Joe Spinelli, Minnie Gehrig, Isadore Druc
  - Local No. 57, New York., 1962-1968 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 50 Includes: Gene Kluger 5/68 Convention, Alex Rose; Herman Dove, 1962 Convention black man speaking; 9th convention Gene Kluger speaking; 9th convention L. 57 delegates
  - Local No. 60 Philadelphia, PA., 1944-1966 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 51 Includes: new officers 12/3/66 Edward Miller, Joseph Mulhall, Harry Platt, John McGraw, Alvin Brown, Leslie Dirsh, John Graham, Robert Casper, Vincent Manzi, Joseph Clifford, Louis Trovarello; Phila
  - Local 64. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 52 Includes: Alfred Smoke, Isadore Drucker, Sherman Wilkinson, Warren Welsh
  - Local 67, Toronto., 1971 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 53 Includes: 14th convention 10/71 Gerald Coleman, Jack MacKeigan, Joe Meslin; 14th convention 10/71 H. Gairey speech; 14th convention 10/71 Jack MacKeigan, Alex Rose
  - Local No. 73. (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 54 Includes: Kaufman millinery shop Richmond, VA; workers of Kaufman and Co. on strike; small snowmen wearing strike sign
  - Local No. 74 Brockville., 1961 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 55 Includes: John B. Stetson Co. and L. 74 negotiating committee 8/17/61; signing with Douglas of Stetson Co.; group party shot
  - Local No. 87 Amesbury, MA., 1946-1962 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 56 Includes: 2/62 Membership Meeting Philip J. Kealy, Frank Cynewski, Carmen Lucia, George Gilbert, Joseph Dollen; winners of Mellimac Scholarship awards 7/62; 7/62 Hawley Patten, Frank Cynewski, Donal
  - Local No. 90 New York, NY., 1969 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 57 Includes: 2/69 Club 90 presents gift to Murray Levine w/ Mannie Savitz and Max Fletcher; Club 90 officer installation: Mannie Savitz, Charles Aschkenos, Murray Levine, Irving Moskowitz, Sol Kuper, M
  - Local No. 91, Sunbury PA., 1962-1963 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 58 Includes: 1963 group shot; 8/63 strike; George Baer with L. 91; negotiating committee 8/10/63/; 3/62 pension checks
  - Local No. 92, New York., 1957-1964 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 59 Includes: Frances Moran addresses meeting 2/25/64; 10th convention Frances Moran; Moran, A. Mendelowitz; 9th convention; 12/57 Sam Kupersmith, Frances Moran; Parer Vale Hats, Peters and Penny, Biltm
  - Local No. 93 Beacon, NY., 1971 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 60 Includes: 14th convention 10/71 Mary Kaplan, Ethel Gell, Angeline Greenman (L. 111), Juanita Smith (L. 111); banquet
  - Local No. 98, New York., 1960-1967 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Collection re-organized - this is formerly box 11, f 61 Includes: Albert Anesh 11/67; 1/65 Jack Stelzer, Harry Effenbach, Milton Hess, Dave Smolin, Louis Levine, Herman Katz, Archie Berman, George Marlin, Nathaniel Spector, Jerry Rosenhaus, Albert Anesh,
  - Local No. 96 Holyoke, MA., 1961 (Box 40, Folder 19)